Welcome to Same's Virtual Tech Garage!
Добро пожаловать в Виртуальный Техно-Гараж Самэ!
This is a secret base where we decode the "why?" hidden in everyday life using VR and science
Это секретная база, где мы разгадываем скрытые в повседневности «почему?» с помощью VR и науки
We cover physics, computer science, and the history of science
Мы изучаем физику, информатику и историю науки
From the rainbow colors of soap bubbles, we explore atoms, earthquakes, and gravity
От радужных переливов мыльных пузырей к атомам, землетрясениям и гравитации
We trace messages from supernova explosions preserved in the deep sea
Мы ищем послания от взрывов сверхновых, сохранившиеся в глубинах океана
Sorting algorithms that reveal the hidden depths of arranging numbers
Алгоритмы сортировки, раскрывающие глубину упорядочивания чисел
To the untold stories of great scientists
И малоизвестные истории великих учёных
For those who want to see the familiar world from a different angle
Для тех, кто хочет взглянуть на привычный мир под другим углом
From everyday wonders to the mysteries of the universe
От повседневных чудес до тайн Вселенной
Won't you join us in exploring the fascination of science and technology?
Давайте вместе исследовать увлекательный мир науки и технологий!